Guide to the May Anti-Slavery manuscript collection, 1749-1933.
May Anti-Slavery manuscript collection
- Series IV. Correspondence and Documents from Other Abolitionists
  - A-F
    - Fisk, Clinton Bowen, November 18, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Fisk, U.M., January 10, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - Fitch, W.R., Undated (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Flader, J.A., April 24, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Flagg, A.S., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Fletcher, Helen E., March 23, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 91)
      Application for teaching position; Recommendations from Beck, Mrs. D.; Field, J.; Holcomb, C.C.; Taft, H.W.; Tucker, Mrs. Geo. J.
    - Forman, J.G., 1865-1866 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Forten, Charlotte L., 1866-1867 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - E.H. Fosdick & Co., November 4, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 94)
      Itemized receipt for Merrick, Chloe
    - Foss, Andrew T., October 24, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Foster, John W., June 18, 1829 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Foster, Richard B., July 24, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Foster, Stephen Symonds, December 28, 1845 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Francis, Charles S., 1854-1860 (Box 13, Folder 106)
      Letter/s to Child, Lydia Maria; Statement of account concerning Lydia Maria Child's published works
    - Franier, Juletta R., April 23, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Freedmen's Aid Reporter, Editor, July 27, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Freedmen's Union Association, Undated (Box 13, Folder 101)
      Constitution
    - Frothingham, Octavius Brooks, March 21, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 102)
      Stevenson, Hannah E.
    - Fulton, Charles C., December 14, 1859 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Fulton, James, August 6, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 104)
      Letter/s to Mott, James
    - Furey, John G., 1867 (Box 13, Folder 105)
      Letter/s to Kimber, Thomas; McKim, James Miller
    - Furness, William Henry, 1859-1867 (Box 13, Folder 107-108)
      Song (of old John Brown); McKim, James Miller; unknown
    - Furney, L.A., February 8, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - G-May, Samuel, Jr.
    - Gage, D.W., November 7, 1864 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Spelman, H.B.
    - Gaines, M.R., February 15, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Garland, Rice, October 14, 1836 (Box 14, Folder 2.5)
      Slave bill of sale
    - Garrett, Thomas, 1858-1860 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Mott, James
    - Garrison, Francis Jackson, 1881-1886 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Letter/s to Fiske, Willard; Harris, George William; Parsons, Sarah Maria
    - Garrison, Wendell Phillips, 1867-1891 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Letter/s to Harris, George William; Lowell, Josephine Shaw; McKim, James Miller
    - Garrison, William Lloyd, 1831-1867 (Box 14, Folder 6-9)
      Letter/s to Abbott, Lyman; Jocelyn, Simeon Smith; McKim, James Miller
      Julian, George Washington
    - Garsed, John, March 2, 1869 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Itemized receipt for Francis George Shaw
    - Gaston, Charity A., May 8, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Letter/s to Holmes, Rev. H.B.
    - Gay, Elizabeth (Mrs. Sydney Howard), April 5, 1860 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Gay, Sydney Howard, 1844-1868 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
      Letter/s to Mr. Garrison; McKim, James Miller
    - Geary, John, March 18, 1854 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Letter/s to Blakely, Angus R.
    - George, Narcissa, February 1, 1870 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Gibbons, Charles, 1862-1863 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      Broadside poem: An Imploration for Our Country; McKim, James Miller
    - Gibbins (?), Isaac L., November 11, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Letter/s to Holmes, H.B.
    - Giddings, Joshua Reed, 1846-1861 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; "To any gentleman of my acquaintance"
    - Giles, James, May 3, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Gillem, Alvan Cullem, December 7, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Gillespie, John, 1867-1868 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      Dibble, O.C.; Horton, Maggie
    - Gillis, C.J., April 9, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Gilman, Jennie, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
      Note concerning teaching position; Recommendation from Hunt, Isaac L.
    - Gilmore, Kate, 1870 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Glavis, George A., July 7, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      Letter/s to Garrison, Wendell Phillips
    - Godfrey, Morella W. (and Mary H.), 1866 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      4 applications for a teaching position; Recommendations from Mosher, John; Steele, Daniel; Sutherland, A.; Wells, William
    - Godwin, Susan, August 22, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Goedel, C., March 7, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Goodrich, Grant, October 8, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      Letter/s to President (?), North Western Freedman's Aid Society
    - Goodwin, Abby, 1861- (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Goodwin, Marva V., September 14, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Gookins, S.B., 1867 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      Tyndale, Sharon
    - Gordon, George William, 1844-1845 (Box 14, Folder 34-36)
      Consular papers
    - Gordon, Maria, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      2 applications for a teaching position; Recommendations from Atwater, W.W. and Wordhiss (?), F.E.
    - Gould, Sarah, January 18, 1868 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Graham, John T., 1866 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Grant, Sarah L., Undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - John A. Gray & Green, December 16, 1868 (Box 14, Folder 40.5)
      Itemized receipt for American Freedman
    - Greeley, Nellie, Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
      2 applications for a teaching position; Recommendations from Balch, Chs. L. and Stevens, A.F.
    - Green, Beriah, May 11, 1857 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Greene, Jennie, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      May, Samuel Joseph; Walden, John Morgan
    - Gregg, E.H., January 16, 1868 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Gregg, Frances E., November 26, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 45)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Spaulding, Geo. And Woodworth, A.B.
    - Gregory, H., 1866-1867 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      Letter/s to Hawkins, William C. (i.e., George); McKim, James Miller
    - Grew, Mary, 1858-1870 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; McKim, Sarah Allibone Speakman; unknown
    - Griffin (?), William, May 9, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Griffith, Goldsborough Sappington, January 16, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Griffith, Mattie, May 5, 1859 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Grossman, H.C., November 29, 1866 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      Letter/s to Tilton, Theodore
    - Gwynne, Eliza, Undated (Box 14, Folder 52)
      Hagerman, Emma L.
    - Hadlock, Mary E., July 30, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Burton, H.N. and Henry, C.J.
    - Hagerman, Emma L., July 26, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Application for a teaching positon; Recommendations from Gwynne, Eliza and Peterson, John
    - Haines, Abner, 1860 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Hale, John A., May 1, 1858 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Receipt for payment received for ten year old male slave
    - Hall, Alice C., December 20, 1869 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Receipt; 6 paychecks
    - Hall, F.E., August 19, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Hall, L.A., 1868 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Hall, R.W., November 18, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Hall, William F., May 28, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Hallowell, Richard Price, 1860-1863 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Letter/s to Brown, Mrs. Mary Ann Day; McKim, James Miller
    - Hallowell, Sarah C., March 3, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Halsey, Mary R., 1866 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Sherwood, Lorenzo; Sothrop, Wm. K.; Wakeley, S.
    - Hamilton, Frank, March 17, 1860 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Hamilton, Hattie E., 1866 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Hooper, E.S.
    - Hammond, Charles G., 1866 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Hammond, H.C., 1866-1867 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Note concerning a teaching position; Recommendation from Graves, A.S.
    - Hampson, Aspinall, April 13, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Hancock, Ann B., August 20, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Manly, R.M.; 5 paychecks; 2 receipts
    - Hankinson, R.H., November 30, 1869 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Receipt; 2 paychecks
    - Harley, John, 1860-1861 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Harlock, Samuel, January 23, 1865 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      Letter/s to Cadbury, B.H.
    - Harper, J.A., May 16, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1868-1869; Harper & Brothers (Box 15, Folder 23)
      Receipts for Belden, Diana A.; New York Branch A.F.U.C; Itemized receipts for Kent, C.J.; New York Branch A.F.U.C.
    - Harrington, Samuel M., 1868 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Harris, Alex T., October 10, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Harris, E.H., August 10, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Harris, Hattie L.S., Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Harris, R.B., March 9, 1850 (Box 15, Folder 27.5)
    - Harris, W.D., May 2, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Harrison, Charles A., Undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Harrison, Timothy, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Hart, William, February 15, 1865 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Haskell, J.C., August 20, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Haskell, Llewellyn Solomon, August 15, 1863 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Haslam, Ann, 1861 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Haven, Ellen B., January 6, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      Letter/s to Hawkins, William George
    - Hawkins, William George, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      Hadlock, Mary E.Burbank, Mr. & Mrs. A.C.; Gilman, Jennie
    - Haydock, Robert, January 24, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Hayes, P.H., March 9, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      Letter/s to Freedmans' Union Commission
      Younglove, Frances E.
    - Haynes, D.C., 1867 (Box 15, Folder 39-40)
      Letter/s to Systematic Aid for the Poor of the South Without Distinction of Color; Abbott, Lyman; McKim, James Miller; unknown
    - Haynes, Mrs. D.C., 1867 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Hays, Weston, 1866-1867 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      Letter/s to McKim, james Miller; Orr, Gov. James L.
    - Henderson, M.S., 1866 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Thompson, Rev. J.P.
    - Henderson, Melitta, September 7, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 44)
      Letter/s to Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Goodrich, G.W.; Peddie, J.; Spencer, H.; Strongh, George H.
    - Brown, Henry Box, Undated (Box 15, Folder 44.5)
      Letter/s to Ticket to "Henry Box Brown's new and original panorama, Mirror of slavery"
    - Henry, Charlotte J., May 1, 1868 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      Hadlock, Mary E.
    - Herndon, D.C., 1868-1869 (Box 15, Folder 46)
      Receipts
    - Hester, Lizzie, November 17, 1869 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Hewitt, A.R., Undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Hewitt, M.T., September 13, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Heywood, E.H., 1860-1861 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Hiatt, J., January 10, 1868 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Hicks, Catherine Mary, 1866-1867 (Box 15, Folder 52)
      Recommendations from Haswell, H.B.; Peck, Francis J.; Thacher, George H.; Williams, M.H.; 1 letter by McDougall, G.P. to Hicks, C.M.; 4 paychecks; 2 receipts
    - Higgins, C.W., December 7, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Higgins, Malvina, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 54)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Beers, Mr. & Mrs. George D.; Hardy, Jane L.; Vinal, K.B.; Wisner, William
    - Higgins, N.S. Ransom, February 5, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Higginson, G., December 9, 1858 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth Storrow, 1859-1867 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Hill, Andrew F., Undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Hill, Isham J., 1868-1869 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Hinton, Richard J., August 31, 1860 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Hite, James, January 13, 1868 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Hobbs, L.M., March 12, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Hobby, C.E., January 13, 1868 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Hodson, John, November 7, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 64)
      Letter/s to Cobb, Nehemiah
    - Hogarth, W., October 1, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Holbrook, Dwight, September 19, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Hollowell, G.W., November 5, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 67)
      Letter/s to Northwest Freedmen's Aid Commission
    - Holmes, H.B., 1866-1867 (Box 15, Folder 68-70)
      Letter/s to Abbott, Lyman; McKim, James Miller; unknown
    - Holton, William H.H., September 17, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Hooper, E.S., September 11, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 72)
      Letter/s to Hamilton, Miss Hattie E.
    - Hooper, E.W., 1866-1870 (Box 15, Folder 73)
      Receipts for Shaw, Francis George; McKim, James Miller
    - Hoover, James, August 31, 1861 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Hooy, H.M., October 13, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Hopkins, Charles T., Undated (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Hopkins, Ellen L., 1867 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Horton, Maggie, 1867-1868 (Box 15, Folder 78)
      Letter/s to Gillespie, John; McKim, James Miller
    - Houghton, Mrs. C.B., January 27, 1866 (Box 15, Folder 79)
      Letter/s to Allan, George H.
    - Hove, Bernard, 1840 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Howard, Oliver Otis, 1866-1868 (Box 15, Folder 81-83)
      Memoranda; Abbott, Lyman; McKim, James Miller
      Johnstone, R.F.; Smith, J. Brinton
    - Howe, Samuel Gridley, August 5, 1863 (Box 15, Folder 84)
      Phillips, Wendell
    - Howes, Nancy L., July 18. 1866 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Hoy, Martha Louisa, August 30, 1867 (Box 15, Folder 86)
      Letter concerning teaching position; Letter concerning change of position by Janney, R.M.
    - Hoyt, George H., 1859 (Box 15, Folder 87)
      Letter/s to Tomlinson, Reuben; unknown
      Barnes, J.W.L.
    - Hudson River Railroad Company, February 22, 1869 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Itemized receipt for Cardoza, T.W.
    - Hughes, Robert, 1826 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Calculation of hire (of slaves) & memo of evidence to accompany the brief appellants
    - Hull, Emily C., April 19, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Humaston, M.L., May 26, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Application for a teaching positon
    - Hunt, B.P., November 2, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Burr, Raymond J.
    - Hunt, Mary L. and Julia C., September 9, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Baker, Osmon C.; Colman, C.S.; Halmon, S.; Leavitt, D.P.; Woolson, Moses
    - Hunt, Mary L., September 14, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Letter/s to Collins, Ellen
    - Hussey, Curtis Grubb, 1867-1868 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Hyatt, Thaddeus, May 24, 1860 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Impey, B., 1867 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ignalls, J.K., May 7, 1860 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ingersoll, John Reed, February 26, 1844 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Inventaire (signed by Mercier and Morauville), Jaunuary 8, 1769 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Inventaire fait a la Guadeloupe au Marquisat de Sante Marie le 12 Decembre 1768. Avec les prix d'estimation des negres existants sur la propriete
    - Inventory, January 10, 1828 (Box 15, Folder 59.5)
      Inventory of Slaves Belonging to Maccaw River
    - Iredell, Laura H., Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ireland, Mary, 1858-1860 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Irish, Elias H., 1860-1866 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Isbell, George E., September 20, 1848 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Isham, Sarah E., August 7, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      Recommendation for a teaching position from Kerr, George
    - Israel, Fielder, 1866-1867 (Box 16, Folder 19-21)
      Letter/s to Hawkins, William George; Kennedy, Crammond; McKim, James Miller; Woolsey, Rev. J.J.
      Anerson, Matilda C.; Estes, E.C.; Rankin, A.N.
    - Ives, Julius, January 9, 1868 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Jaccard, E., 1866 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Jackson, Francis, November 3, 1859 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Jackson, James, July 11, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Jackson, Mary E., July 26, 1869 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Jackson, W.C., July 10, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Jamison, Robert, August 3, 1827 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      Letter/s to Watson, Joseph
    - Janney, R.M., June 6, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Hoy, Martha Louisa
    - Janney, Samuel McPherson, December 12, 1843 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Jay, John, June 22, 1865 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Jay, William, 1843-1846 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Jenkins, J. Foster, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Jenkins, J.M., January 24, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      Letter/s to American Union Commission
    - Jenkins, Josiah Whipple, November 1852 (Box 16, Folder 34.1)
      Obituary
      Brown, John
    - Jennings, G. Mifflin, January 28, 1870 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Jewell, Betty, June 27. 1776 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      Indenture between Betty Jewell and her daughter Elizabeth for the gift to Elizabeth of a mulatto slave named Rose
    - Jocelyn, Simeon Smith, January 22, 1870 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      Buffum, Arnold; Garrison, William Lloyd; Philleo, Prudence Crandall
    - John Brown's Grave, October 15, 1901 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      Printed in Ithaca Daily Journal
    - Johnson, Albert R., July 17, 1869 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      Receipts; 3 paychecks
    - Johnson, Arthur A., 1869-1870 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Johnson, Ezra A., December 30, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Johnson, Francis P., 1869-1870 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Johnson, Jane, September 13, 1855 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Johnson, Mattie, March 9, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Johnson, N.M., November 1, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Johnson, Oliver, 1846-1869 (Box 16, Folder 46-53)
      Clemmer, M.K.; Orton, Caroline S.
    - Johnson, Rowland, January 18, 1861 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Johnson, Brooke & Co., August 2, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Johnston, Kittie, August 31, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 56)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Baker, Charles L.; Miss Johnston's record
    - Johnston, N.R., December 29, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Johnstone, R.F., January 28, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 58)
      Letter/s to Howard, Oliver Otis
    - Jones, Benjamin S., 1847-1861 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Jones, Cornelia, 1868-1869 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Jones, E.B., 1869 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Jones, Emma D., April 30, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Jones, Garner A., April 22, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Jones, John, Jr., 1870 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Jones, Nancy, 1869-1870 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Josselyn, George, December 30, 1799 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Julian, George Washington, June 23, 1875 (Box 16, Folder 67)
      Letter/s to Garrison, William Lloyd
    - Kay, Arthur, October 23, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Kellogg, John R., January 28, 1860 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Kelly, Ophelia, 1869-1870 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Kemp, Agnes, November 25, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Kendrick, James Ryland, 1866-1867 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Kennedy, A.W., February 8, 1866 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Kennedy, Crammond, 1866-1868 (Box 16, Folder 74-76)
      King, Esther E.
    - Kennedy, H.A., October 13, 1867 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Kennedy, Thomas, 1866-1867 (Box 16, Folder 78-79)
      Letter/s to Abbott, Lyman; McKim, James Miller; Patterson, Robert Wilson
    - Kent, C.J., November 21, 1868 (Box 16, Folder 80)
      Letter/s to Receipt; 2 paychecks
    - Ketchum, Alexander Phoenix, 1866-1867 (Box 16, Folder 81)
      Letter/s to Bowen, Sayles Jenks; McKim, James Miller; Sprague, John Titcomb
    - Ketler, E.L, June 9, 1861 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Kimball, John, January 19, 1867 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Letter/s to Newton, A.E.
      Morris, M.L.
    - Kimball, Mary J., September 12, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Beecher, Thomas K.; Gleason, R.B.; Keyes, J.J.
    - Kimball, Mary R., February 12, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Kimber, Thomas, 1867-1868 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
      Furey, John G.
    - King, Emily and Mary, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Barnum, H.A.; Fishie, George M.; Palmer, Allen; Parker, Lorenzo
    - King, Esther E., 1866 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Recommendations for a teaching position from Howland, J.K.; Nelson, Harriet; Williams, S.G.; letter by Allen Gray to Miss King; letter by Crammond Kennedy to J.J. Woolsey
    - King, F., September 27, 1867 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - King, Francis T., 1866-1868 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - King, John G., December 5, 1881 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Kingsbury, E., 1867-1868 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Kinman, O.D., June 4, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Knight, H.B., 1866 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Kyrk, Hattie E., April 6, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      2 letters of application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Crane, Jonathan and Osborn, H.
    - La Fresnaye, April 27, 1802 (Box 17, Folder 14.1)
      Letter/s to Vente des meubles, effets, et esvlaves de M. La Fresnaye
    - Lambert, Margaret F., August 10, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Burnhame, Jonas
    - Lane, Ella H., August 31, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Application for a teaching position; Recommendation from Pinkham, G.W.
    - Lane, Whitmel, March 1, 1870 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - LaPeue, Mary C., 1869-1870 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Larkin, Joseph F., 1866-1867 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Larned, Edwin C., December 24, 1867 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Lawton, Bella C., 1866 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Applications for a teaching position to Shaw, Francis G. and Woolsey, James J.; Recommendations from Coe, Richard; Davis, Park; Howard, S.E.; Rees, Henry E.; Smith, J. Hyatt; Waterman, E.L.
    - Lazenby, James E., 1868-1869 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      Receipts; Collins, Ellen
    - Leavitt, Joshua, November 17, 1859 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Letter/s to Spring, Marcus
      Orton, Caroline S.
    - Lee, Joseph E., 1870 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Lee, S.P., 1866-1869 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      Receipt; McKim, James Miller; Shaw, Francis George
    - Leeds Anti-Slavery Association, February 22, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      Objects and rules of the Leeds Anti-Slavery Association..
    - Le Moyne, Francis Julius, April 4, 1838 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Leonard, Ellen D., 1868-1870 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Leonard, William H., 1860 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Lesley, Peter, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Lewis, Abbie A., August 1866 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      Letter/s to Application for a teaching position; Recommendations from Mason, S.R. and Stockwell, G.S.
    - No Folder 30 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, Grace Anna, 1860-1861 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Lieler, L.S., July 11, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Linton, M.B., 1860-1861 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      Letter/s to McKim, James Miller; Still, William
    - Littell, William N., October 11, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Andrew Little & Brother, December 10, 1868 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      Itemized receipt
    - Llenas, Jose, 1841 (Box 17, Folder 38-40)
      Letter/s to Arzceto, Dr. Jose; Engeles, Jose; Paxoto, Juan
    - Lloyd, Henry Demarest, June 6, 1872 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      Petition for the conference to defeat re-election of Ulysses S. Grant
    - Lockwood, Samuel D., November 25, 1867 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Logan, Isaac, 1867 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      Letter/s to Bowen, Henry Chandler; Johnson, Oliver; McKim, James Miller
    - Lomax, Edward, 1869-1870 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Long, J.D., September 18, 1861 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Long, Walter R., 1868-1869 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Longley, J.G., 1866-1867 (Box 17, Folder 47)
      Extract from the Fox will; McKim, James Miller
    - Loomis, G.P., January 10, 1868 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Lord, Julia A., 1867 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Loud, F., April 12, 1866 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Loud, Libbie A., 1866 (Box 17, Folder 51)
      Applications for a teaching position; recommendation from G.A. Scovill, Charles H. Guile, E.D. Babcock, D.F. Tompkins, H.S. Henlee, and F.J. Mankry